inmotionflowers.co.za 2015-03-17

# Privacy Policy | inMotion Flowers

Please read this privacy notice and our [Terms & Conditions](http://www.inmotionflowers.co.za/terms/) carefully before using this website. Your privacy and security is extremely important to us, and we will only use the information you provide us, to provide you with a more streamlined online experience and better customer service.

## Your Personal Information

When you place an order, register on our website or subscribe to our newsletter; you need to provide us with certain personal information. We only ever request details that are necessary to fulfil your order successfully and to provide you with the best customer service possible. Rest assured though, we respect your privacy and your details are safe with us.

## When You Place an Order

We require your name, contact details (email address and telephone number) and which country you are in. This is so that we can communicate effectively with you regarding your order. We also need the recipient’s name, contact details and address to successfully fulfil your order.  For your own safety, we do not collect any financial information such as credit card details. This is handled by our secure payment gateway, [VCS (Virtual Card Services)](https://www.vcs.co.za/).

## When You Register

Registering on our website has the following benefits:

  * Proceed through checkout faster when making a purchase
  * Check the status of orders
  * View past orders so you don't send the same gift twice
  * Choose to be notified of updates and special promotions via our newsletter (optional)
  * Make changes to your account information
  * Store alternative addresses to easily send to multiple family members and friends
  * Manage your product reviews, tags and wishlist

When you register, you will provide us with the same contact details as you would when you place an order, plus you have the option of adding additional information to your profile to help us streamline our service. Please note, we do not collect or store any financial information such as credit card details.

The contact information we collect will be used to contact you to update you on your order status, query or complete a delivery where the recipient cannot be found, or if further information may be required. This information may be used to send you occasional news about updates to our website, promotional offers or specials. At any time you may choose not to receive these notices; see the opt-out section below.

## What Else We Collect

We collect and store your IP address to help us identify you and your shopping cart. Our website also uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart and to tailor our content to your specific interests.

Information such as occasion type (Birthday, Valentine’s Day, Mothers Day, etc.), products purchased, any relevant promotion or discount reference may also be collected, and the recipient's name, address and telephone number is also stored.

The site may also collect certain information about your visit, such as the name of the Internet service provider and the Internet Protocol (IP) address through which you access the Internet; the date and time you access the site; the pages that you visit while at the site and the Internet address of the website from which you came to our site. This information is used to help improve our website and service, analyse trends, and administer the site in general.

## How We Use this Information

When you use our website, you acknowledge and accept that any personal information supplied to us is done so voluntarily. inMotion Flowers will only disclose information provided by users of this website to business partners and no personal information provided will be disclosed to third parties. inMotion Flowers may use the information that you provide to communicate with you from time to time or to respond to your requests for information and orders. You may indicate at any time that you do not wish to receive such communications. See opt-out section below.

## Opt-out

It is important to us that we do not send any of our customers anything they do not want to receive. So should you no longer wish to receive any of our communications, such as our newsletter, updates to our website, special offers and promotions, etc.; you may opt-out of these communications at any time by emailing us at: [info@inmotionflowers.co.za](mailto:info@inmotionflowers.co.za), or adjusting your account settings.

If you would like to change or update any of the information you have submitted, or delete your account entirely, you can also do this by sending us an email to the above address.

## Applicable Law

Our privacy policy and terms and conditions shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the Republic of South Africa without giving effect to the principles of conflicts of laws. By using this website, you hereby consent to the exclusive jurisdiction of the High Court of the Republic of South Africa in respect of any disputes arising in connection with this web site.

## Contacting Us

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy, our practices, or your dealings with us, you may contact inMotion Flowers customer care at: [info@inmotionflowers.co.za](mailto:info@inmotionflowers.co.za).
